UI Designer Software Engineer **Electronic Engineer**

LOOUIS LOW



ABOUT ME

II have worked in an embedded system domain for ten years. I am primarily prototyping Electronic applications for Automation, Monitoring and Signal Processing. I also make UI Designs and Frontend-Dev for Embedded Applications, Web Apps, Websites, TV Apps, Mobile Apps, and as well as Graphic Designs to create materials for marketing and user interface.

CONTACT ME

PHONE NO (+6) 016 4910 454

EMAIL

loouis@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://loouislow81.github.io

SOCIAL

dev.to/loouislow twitter.com/loouislow github.com/loouislow81



EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer (architect) dogsbark Canada Embedded Design, Firmware Design, Prototyping and Auto-2004-2020

mation. Machine Learning and Sound Effect middleware en-

gineering.

Software Engineer (frontend) Goody Malaysia Craft UI Material Design & UI Design System. Pure CSS FX 2016-2017 without JS. Create custom frontend devtools and boiler-2018-2019 plates with added CLI automation.

Internet Mastermind

Software Engineer (frontend)

Malaysia

2014-2015

Implement UI and UX for marketing applications with Bootstrap UI framework. Frontend and Backend UI prototyping.

Custom landing page web design for marketer.

EDUCATIONS

Shrewsbury College Visual Art & Design

2008-2009

I also am artist. I gave myself a chance to step into a little bit deeper into the art. Also, I am a perfectionist either in UI or

UX.

Univ. Manchester

Electrical & Electronic Engineering

UK

2002-2005

I was always wanting to be an inventor like robotic, anything, since I was a little kid. But, well, they all came true. I just kept

doing it. Never stop.

Chung Ling H. S.

Malaysia

1995-2000

Just an ordinary student not very fond of school subjects, beside the computer programming and science classes.

Never a good chance in Art class.

SKILLS

Embedded Development FPGA Protyping

Web Development

Software Development

Front-End, UI & UX Designs

Firmware, Essential for Engineering

KNOWLEDGE

PCB/Schematic Design

Firmware Design

Embedded Design

Linux

Electronic

Electronic

Electronic

Debian

Docker

Containerization

Git

Source Versioning Control

C, C++, Vala

Firmware, Software Development

Bash

JavaScripts, NodeJS

Python

Automation Scripting

Frontend Development

Software Prototyping

HTML, Nunjucks, CSS, Sass

Yogurt, Bootstrap

Adobe PS/AI, Framer **UI Mockup & Prototyping**

Frontend Development

Web Design & Styling